<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
     <string-array name="tree_uris">
        <item name="bristlecone_pine"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/search?tbm=isch&hl=en&source=hp&biw=1639&bih=800&q=bluespruce&gbv=2&oq=bluespruce&aq=f&aqi=g-s10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0i10l10.901.4133.0.4408.14.11.1.1.1.0.184.999.8j3.11.0...0.0.Vkr6yjq1gPs#hl=en&gbv=2&tbm=isch&sa=1&q=bristlecone+pine&oq=bristlecone+pine&aq=f&aqi=g10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0l10.19703.21712.1.21797.16.10.0.6.6.0.131.955.7j3.10.0...0.0.839HRhgRJiI&pbx=1&bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.,cf.osb&fp=8bc87984190bfcc2&biw=1639&bih=800]]></item>
        <item name="blue_spruce"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/search?tbm=isch&hl=en&source=hp&biw=1639&bih=800&q=bluespruce&gbv=2&oq=bluespruce&aq=f&aqi=g-s10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0i10l10.901.4133.0.4408.14.11.1.1.1.0.184.999.8j3.11.0...0.0.Vkr6yjq1gPs#hl=en&gbv=2&tbm=isch&sa=X&ei=4vSqT_3bOqKC2AW5zpGrBw&ved=0CEIQBSgA&q=blue+spruce&spell=1&bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.,cf.osb&fp=8bc87984190bfcc2&biw=1639&bih=800]]></item>
        <item name="douglas_fir"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/search?tbm=isch&hl=en&source=hp&biw=1639&bih=800&q=bluespruce&gbv=2&oq=bluespruce&aq=f&aqi=g-s10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0i10l10.901.4133.0.4408.14.11.1.1.1.0.184.999.8j3.11.0...0.0.Vkr6yjq1gPs#hl=en&gbv=2&tbm=isch&sa=X&ei=R_WqT9SKAYLE2wX-s5XKCA&ved=0CEEQvwUoAQ&q=douglas-fir&spell=1&bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.,cf.osb&fp=8bc87984190bfcc2&biw=1639&bih=800]]></item>
        <item name="engelmann_spruce"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/search?tbm=isch&hl=en&source=hp&biw=1639&bih=800&q=bluespruce&gbv=2&oq=bluespruce&aq=f&aqi=g-s10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0i10l10.901.4133.0.4408.14.11.1.1.1.0.184.999.8j3.11.0...0.0.Vkr6yjq1gPs#hl=en&gbv=2&tbm=isch&sa=1&q=engelmann+spruce&oq=engelmann&aq=0&aqi=g10&aql=&gs_l=img.3.0.0l10.6022.9609.7.10319.13.9.2.2.2.0.200.1604.0j8j1.9.0...0.0.hcwjRC94hVQ&pbx=1&bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.,cf.osb&fp=17fea353a1d5bf15&biw=800&bih=766]]></item>
        <item name="limber_pine"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/search?tbm=isch&hl=en&source=hp&biw=1639&bih=800&q=bluespruce&gbv=2&oq=bluespruce&aq=f&aqi=g-s10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0i10l10.901.4133.0.4408.14.11.1.1.1.0.184.999.8j3.11.0...0.0.Vkr6yjq1gPs#hl=en&gbv=2&tbm=isch&sa=1&q=limber+pine&oq=limber+pine&aq=f&aqi=g6g-m1g-S3&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0l6j0i5j0i24l3.8868.11963.9.12104.15.13.2.0.0.0.203.1824.0j12j1.13.0...0.0.X-vMCYag4JI&pbx=1&bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.,cf.osb&fp=17fea353a1d5bf15&biw=800&bih=766]]></item>
        <item name="lodge_pole_pine"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/search?tbm=isch&hl=en&source=hp&biw=1639&bih=800&q=bluespruce&gbv=2&oq=bluespruce&aq=f&aqi=g-s10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0i10l10.901.4133.0.4408.14.11.1.1.1.0.184.999.8j3.11.0...0.0.Vkr6yjq1gPs#hl=en&gbv=2&tbm=isch&sa=1&q=lodgepole+pine&oq=lodgepole+pine&aq=f&aqi=g10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0l10.10664.13902.11.14094.14.8.0.6.6.0.167.1041.0j8.8.0...0.0.3q3zexeuOis&pbx=1&bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.,cf.osb&fp=17fea353a1d5bf15&biw=800&bih=766]]></item>
        <item name="narrow_leaf_cottonwood"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/search?tbm=isch&hl=en&source=hp&biw=1639&bih=800&q=bluespruce&gbv=2&oq=bluespruce&aq=f&aqi=g-s10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0i10l10.901.4133.0.4408.14.11.1.1.1.0.184.999.8j3.11.0...0.0.Vkr6yjq1gPs#hl=en&gbv=2&tbm=isch&sa=1&q=narrowleaf+cottonwood&oq=narrowleaf+cottonwood&aq=f&aqi=g1g-S1&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0j0i24.10837.14291.13.14450.21.13.0.8.8.0.181.1710.0j13.13.0...0.0.JFTDz-rgvbQ&pbx=1&bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.,cf.osb&fp=17fea353a1d5bf15&biw=800&bih=766]]></item>
        <item name="quaking_aspen"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/search?tbm=isch&hl=en&source=hp&biw=1639&bih=800&q=bluespruce&gbv=2&oq=bluespruce&aq=f&aqi=g-s10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0i10l10.901.4133.0.4408.14.11.1.1.1.0.184.999.8j3.11.0...0.0.Vkr6yjq1gPs#hl=en&gbv=2&tbm=isch&sa=1&q=quaking+aspen&oq=quaking+aspen&aq=f&aqi=g10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0l10.8863.10345.15.10759.13.9.0.4.4.0.208.1267.0j8j1.9.0...0.0.TJyFUZA6ZSI&pbx=1&bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.,cf.osb&fp=17fea353a1d5bf15&biw=800&bih=766]]></item>
        <item name="pinon_pine"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/search?tbm=isch&hl=en&source=hp&biw=1639&bih=800&q=bluespruce&gbv=2&oq=bluespruce&aq=f&aqi=g-s10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0i10l10.901.4133.0.4408.14.11.1.1.1.0.184.999.8j3.11.0...0.0.Vkr6yjq1gPs#hl=en&gbv=2&tbm=isch&sa=1&q=pinon+pine&oq=pinon+pine&aq=f&aqi=g2g-S8&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0l2j0i24l8.11263.12895.17.12970.10.8.0.2.2.0.195.1006.1j7.8.0...0.0.qKF851iOtJ4&pbx=1&bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.,cf.osb&fp=17fea353a1d5bf15&biw=800&bih=766]]></item>
        <item name="plains_cottonwood"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/search?tbm=isch&hl=en&source=hp&biw=1639&bih=800&q=bluespruce&gbv=2&oq=bluespruce&aq=f&aqi=g-s10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0i10l10.901.4133.0.4408.14.11.1.1.1.0.184.999.8j3.11.0...0.0.Vkr6yjq1gPs#hl=en&gbv=2&tbm=isch&sa=1&q=plains+cottonwood&oq=plains+cottonwood&aq=f&aqi=g4g-S1&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0l4j0i24.6903.8494.19.8632.17.14.0.2.2.1.203.2202.0j13j1.14.0...0.0.BExgrVH_7KA&pbx=1&bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.,cf.osb&fp=17fea353a1d5bf15&biw=800&bih=766]]></item>
        <item name="ponderosa_pine"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/search?tbm=isch&hl=en&source=hp&biw=1639&bih=800&q=bluespruce&gbv=2&oq=bluespruce&aq=f&aqi=g-s10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0i10l10.901.4133.0.4408.14.11.1.1.1.0.184.999.8j3.11.0...0.0.Vkr6yjq1gPs#hl=en&gbv=2&tbm=isch&sa=1&q=ponderosa+pine&oq=ponderosa+pine&aq=f&aqi=g10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0l10.7134.9521.21.9633.14.10.0.4.4.0.146.1241.0j10.10.0...0.0.oIkVSkgnuq8&pbx=1&bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.,cf.osb&fp=17fea353a1d5bf15&biw=800&bih=766]]></item>
        <item name="rocky_mountain_juniper"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/search?tbm=isch&hl=en&source=hp&biw=1639&bih=800&q=bluespruce&gbv=2&oq=bluespruce&aq=f&aqi=g-s10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0i10l10.901.4133.0.4408.14.11.1.1.1.0.184.999.8j3.11.0...0.0.Vkr6yjq1gPs#hl=en&gbv=2&tbm=isch&sa=1&q=rocky+mountain+juniper&oq=rocky+mountain+juniper&aq=f&aqi=g7g-m2g-S1&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0l7j0i5l2j0i24.8801.12259.23.12346.22.16.0.6.6.0.180.2085.0j15.15.0...0.0.VNpqpomAeRk&pbx=1&bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.,cf.osb&fp=17fea353a1d5bf15&biw=800&bih=766]]></item>
        <item name="subalpine_fir"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/search?tbm=isch&hl=en&source=hp&biw=1639&bih=800&q=bluespruce&gbv=2&oq=bluespruce&aq=f&aqi=g-s10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0i10l10.901.4133.0.4408.14.11.1.1.1.0.184.999.8j3.11.0...0.0.Vkr6yjq1gPs#hl=en&gbv=2&tbm=isch&sa=1&q=subalpine+fir&oq=subalpine+fir&aq=f&aqi=g4g-m1g-S5&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0l4j0i5j0i24l5.8726.11200.25.11281.13.10.0.3.3.0.152.1119.0j9.9.0...0.0.l-OW9yzNt9Q&pbx=1&bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.,cf.osb&fp=17fea353a1d5bf15&biw=800&bih=766]]></item>
        <item name="white_fir"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/search?tbm=isch&hl=en&source=hp&biw=1639&bih=800&q=bluespruce&gbv=2&oq=bluespruce&aq=f&aqi=g-s10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0i10l10.901.4133.0.4408.14.11.1.1.1.0.184.999.8j3.11.0...0.0.Vkr6yjq1gPs#hl=en&gbv=2&tbm=isch&sa=1&q=white+fir&oq=white+fir&aq=f&aqi=g10&aql=&gs_l=img.3..0l10.5338.6084.27.6209.9.8.0.0.0.0.249.1079.0j6j1.7.0...0.0.V1Ov7YHxlRI&pbx=1&bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.,cf.osb&fp=17fea353a1d5bf15&biw=800&bih=766]]></item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="tree_names">
        <item name="bristlecone_pine">Bristlecone Pine</item>
        <item name="blue_spruce">Blue Spruce</item>
        <item name="douglas_fir">Douglas Fir</item>
        <item name="engelmann_spruce">Engelmann Spruce</item>
        <item name="limber_pine">Limber Pine</item>
        <item name="lodge_pole_pine">Lodgepole Pine</item>
        <item name="narrow_leaf_cottonwood">Narrowleaf Cottonwood</item>
        <item name="quaking_aspen">Quaking Aspen</item>
        <item name="pinon_pine">Pinon Pine</item>
        <item name="plains_cottonwood">Plains Cottonwood</item>
        <item name="ponderosa_pine">Ponderosa Pine</item>
        <item name="rocky_mountain_juniper">Rocky Mountain Juniper</item>
        <item name="subalpine_fir">Subalpine Fir</item>
        <item name="white_fir">White Fir</item>
    </string-array>
    
        <string-array name="searchable_terms">
            <item>bark_color</item> 
  			<item>bark_texture</item>
  			<item>bark_thickness</item>
  			<item>leaf_color</item>
  			<item >leaf_texture</item>
  			<item >leaf_length</item>
  			<item >fruit_shape</item>
  			<item >fruit_color</item>
  			<item >fruit_length</item>
  			<item >fruit_seed</item>
  			<item >elevation</item>
  			<item>height</item>
  			<item>habitat_region</item>
  			<item >habitat_temperature</item>
  			<item >fire_susceptibility</item>
        </string-array>
        
        <string-array name="tree_info">
            <item name="bristlecone_pine">Bristlecone Pine (Pinus aristata)\nBark: Light gray and smooth when young; red-brown with irregular, scaly ridges when mature.\nLeaves: Evergreen needles are dark with white lines, they have white pitch dots on both surfaces; to 1-inch long; crowded in a long, dense mass along the twig; generally 5 in a bundle.\nFruit: Cylindrical, dark purple-brown cones; 2 to 3 inches long; 4-sided cone scales with stiff curved points; brown seeds with black mottling and detachable wing.\nElevation: 9,200 to 11,800 feet\nHeight: 15 to 30 feet\nHabitat: On exposed, cold, dry, rocky slopes and high mountain ridges up to timberline; in pure stands or with limber pine.\nRelation to Fire: Fires virtually nonexistent in these areas due to low temperatures and a short growing season.\n</item>
        	<item name="blue_spruce">Blue Spruce (Picea pungens)\nBark: Gray-brown with thick scales on mature trees. \nLeaves: Evergreen needles are blue or light green with white lines; 1 to 1-1/4 inches long with thin, long, flexible and irregularly toothed scales; contains paired, long-winged seeds. \nFruit: Shiny light brown, cylindrical cones; 2 to 4 inches long with thin, long, flexible and irregularly toothed scales; contains paired, long-winged seeds. \nElevation: 6,700 to 11,500 feet. \nHeight: 70 to 115 feet. \nHabitat: Well-drained, sandy soils; moist sites of narrow bottomlands or along mountains streams; often in pure stands. \nRelation to Fire: Easily killed by fire due to thin bark, shallow roots and low branches.</item>
	        <item name="douglas_fir">Douglas-fir (Pseudotsuga menziesii)  \nBark: Gray and smooth with resin blisters on young trees; red-brown, very thick and deeply furrowed with broad, often corky ridges at maturity. \nLeaves: Evergreen needles are to 1-inch long with bracts at the base. \nFruit: Light brown, short-stalked cones that hang down from the branches; 1-1/3 to 3 inches long; many thin, rounded cone scales on top of long, 3-pointed, winged seeds that stick out beyond scales. \nElevation: 6,000 to 9,500 feet. \nHeight: 100 to 130 feet. \nHabitat: Rocky soils of moist northern slopes; in pure stands and mixed conifer forests. \nRelation to Fire: Thin, resinous bark of young trees makes them highly susceptible to fire; after 40 years, trees have developed a very thick layer of bark to protect them during hot ground and surface fires.</item>
	        <item name="engelmann_spruce">Engelmann Spruce (Picea engelmannii)  \nBark: Gray-brown, thick, with flaky scales.\nLeaves: Evergreen needles are deep blue-green with white lines; 5/8 to 1 inch long; slender, sharp and flexible; skunk-like odor when crushed. \nFruit: Light chestnut-colored, oblong cones; 1 to 2 inches long; in upper part of crown with scales that are paper-thin and ragged along the outer edge. Seeds have a single, long and well-developed wing. \nElevation: 8,000 to 11,000 feet. \nHeight: 45 to 130 feet. \nHabitat: High, cold forest environments on moist, northern slopes; with subalpine fir and other conifers. \nRelation to Fire: Generally killed by fire due to thin bark, shallow roots, low growing branches, tendency to grow in dense stands and support heavy lichen growth. Large trees may survive low-intensity fires.</item>
	        <item name="limber_pine">Limber Pine (Pinus flexilis)  \nBark: Light gray, thin and smooth on young trees; at maturity, dark brown, thick and furrowed into scaly ridges. Young branches are very flexible, hence the name. \nLeaves: Slender evergreen needles are blue-green with white lines on all surfaces; 2 to 3 inches long, typically 5 in a bundle. \nFruit: Yellow-brown, egg-shaped cones; thick, rounded cone scales that end in a blunt point; seeds are large with a very short wing. \nElevation: 5,000 - 12,000. \nHeight: 40 to 50 feet. \nHabitat: Nutrient-poor soils on dry, rocky slopes; ridges up to timberline and often pure stands. \nRelation to Fire: Young trees can be killed by any fire; mature trees can only survive low-intensity fires, but due to the sparse fuels, late snow-melt and short growing season, this species is rarely affected.</item>
	        <item name="lodge_pole_pine">Lodgepole Pine (Pinus contorta)  \nBark: Light brown, thin with many small scales. \nLeaves: Evergreen needles are yellow to dark green; 1 to 3 inches long; sharply pointed, stiff, stout, slightly flattened and often twisted; 2 needles per bundle. \nFruit: Shiny, yellow-brown, egg-shaped, serotinous* cones; to 2 inches long with raised, rounded cone scales and a tiny point. *Seeds released from cones by exposure to extreme heat. \nElevation: 6,000 to 11,000 feet. \nHeight: 20 to 80 feet. \nHabitat: Mostly well-drained soils in high elevations, often in pure stands. \nRelation to Fire: Ground fires kill many trees due to thin bark. New stands quickly establish when cones open and seeds are released.</item>
	        <item name="narrow_leaf_cottonwood">Narrowleaf Cottonwood (Populus angustifolia)  \nBark: Yellow-green and smooth on young trees; thick, gray-brown and furrowed with interlacing ridges at maturity. \nLeaves: Broad-leaf foliage is shiny green with a pale underside; narrow and 2 to 3 inches long; lance shaped with a fine, serrated edge and a pointed tip. \nFruit: Light brown, hairless fruit; inch long; many broad, egg-shaped capsules that mature in the spring, then split into two parts containing many cotton-like seeds. \nElevation: 5,000 to 8,000 feet. \nHeight: Up to 60 feet. \nHabitat: Moist soils along streams; can often be found with willows and alders in coniferous forests. \nRelation to Fire: Severe fires can easily kill both young and mature trees. Young trees are able to sprout from roots and/or branches after a fire.</item>
	        <item name="quaking_aspen">Quaking Aspen (Populus tremuloides)  \nBark: Green-white, smooth and thin with raised dark patches; on very large trees, trunk base is often gray, thick and furrowed. \nLeaves: Broad-leaf foliage is bright green above and dull green below; rounded with a pointed tip, 1 to 3 inches wide on a flattened leaf head; nearly round and sawtoothed. \nFruit: Fruit are catkins; up to 4 inches long; many light green capsules contain 6 to 8 tiny, cotton-like seeds. \nElevation: 6,500 to 11,500 feet. \nHeight: 35 to 50 feet. \nHabitat: Many soil types, especially on well-drained, sandy and gravelly slopes; often in pure stands. \nRelation to Fire: Easily killed by fire, but quick to send out many sucker shoots; readily colonizes after a fire.</item>
	        <item name="pinon_pine">Piñon Pine (Pinus edulis)  \nBark: Gray, smooth and thin when young; red-brown, rough and furrowed into scaly ridges at maturity. \nLeaves: Evergreen needles are stout and light green; 1 to 1-1/2 inches long; 2 in a bundle. \nFruit: Cones are yellow-brown, unique, short and squatty; 1 to 2 inches long. Each cone contains 10 to 20 large, edible, oily seeds. \nElevation: 5,200 to 9,000 feet. \nHeight: 20 to 50 feet. \nHabitat: Open woodlands; alone or with junipers on dry rocky foothills, mesas and plateaus. \nRelation to Fire: Easily killed by fire due to thin bark, relatively flammable foliage and accumulation of dead lower branches.</item>
	        <item name="plains_cottonwood">Plains Cottonwood (Populus deltoides)  \nBark: Green-yellow and smooth while young; dark gray, thick, rough and deeply furrowed at maturity. \nLeaves: Broad-leafed foliage is glossy and yellow-green; 3 to 6 inches long, 4 to 6 inches wide; toothed margins. \nFruit: Inch long with capsules containing 3 to 4 valves; many tiny, cotton-like seeds inside valves. \nElevation: 3,500 to 6,500 feet. \nHeight: 36 to 190 feet. \nHabitat: Found in floodplains, bordering streams, near springs and in moist woodlands; pure stands or with willows. \nRelation to Fire: Generally killed by fire; very poor sprouting response.</item>
	        <item name="ponderosa_pine">Ponderosa Pine (Pinus ponderosa)  \nBark: Dark on young trees; nearly 3 inches thick, red-orange and furrowed into large, flat scaly plates on mature trees. \nLeaves: Evergreen needles are stiff, dark yellow-green; 3 to 7 inches long; typically in bundles of 3 that form tufts near the ends of branches. \nFruit: Light red-brown cones; 3 to 4 inches long; egg-shaped with scales that are tipped by a sharp point; small, long-winged seeds. \nElevation: 6,300 to 9,500 feet. \nHeight: 40 to 160 feet. \nHabitat: Dry, nutrient poor soils in open park-like stands or with Douglas-fir, Rocky Mountain juniper and spruce. \nRelation to Fire: Resistant to fire, due to open crowns, thick, insulating bark, self-pruning branches, high moisture content in the leaves and thick bud scales.</item>
	        <item name="rocky_mountain_juniper">Rocky Mountain Juniper (Juniperus scopulorum)  \nBark: Gray-brown, thin, fibrous; shreds with a red-brown color underneath. \nLeaves: Evergreen scalelike needles are small, gray-green or silvery. \nFruit: Blue-gray berries; waxy and juicy; inch in diameter; typically two-seeded. \nElevation: 5,000 to 9,000 feet. \nHeight: 20 to 50 feet. \nHabitat: Grows on rocky soils in the foothills and on the plains; often associated with piñon pines. \nRelation to Fire: The resinous wood is very flammable. Low intensity fires easily kill this tree due to its thin bark and compact crown.</item>
	        <item name="subalpine_fir">Subalpine Fir (Abies lasiocarpa)  \nBark: Gray and smooth with resin blisters while young; shallow fissures and scaly when mature. \nLeaves: Evergreen needles are dark, blue-green with silvery lines on both surfaces; 1 to 1-1/2 inches long; flat and blunt tipped; crowded and curved upward on twigs at nearly right angles. \nFruit: Upright, cylindrical, very dark purple, 2 to 4 inches long in the upper part of the crown; fine, hairy, cone scales; long, broad-winged seeds. These deciduous cones fall apart when mature so they are rarely found on the ground. \nElevation: 8,000 to 12,000 feet. \nHeight: 60 to 100 feet. \nHabitat: Cold, high elevation forests; with Engelmann spruce and other conifers. \nRelation to Fire: Generally killed by low-intensity fires because of thin, flammable bark, shallow roots, low-growing branches and dense growing conditions. Seeds readily germinate on recently burned ground.</item>
	        <item name="white_fir">White Fir (Abies concolor)  \nBark: Light gray and smooth with resin blisters on young trees; deeply furrowed into corky ridges and orange cracks when mature. \nLeaves: Evergreen needles are light blue-green or silvery with white lines on both surfaces; 1 to 3 inches long; flat and rounded. \nFruit: Oblong, olive-green to blue cones; 3 to 5 inches long; upright on topmost twigs; fine, hairy cone scales; paired, long-winged seeds. \nElevation: 7,900 to 10,200 feet. \nHeight: 60 to 125 feet. \nHabitat: Moist soils of high mountain valleys; in pure stands and with other firs. \nRelation to Fire: Young are usually killed by low-intensity fires due to thin, resin blistered bark and drooping lower branches; mature trees are moderately fire tolerant.</item>
        </string-array>
    
</resources>